以下是《无耻家庭》前情提要
This is what you missed last week on Shameless.
非常赞的一集
It was a great episode.
黛比  停下
Oh, Debbie. Debbie, stop.
-难道你不想要吗  -将来某一天
- Don't you want to? - Someday.
-为什么不是现在  -因为你才13岁
- Well, why not now? - 'Cause you're 13.
原来我还有1/32的梅诺米尼人[北美印第安人]血统呢
It turns out I'm 1/32 Menominee Indian.
你本人更性感
You're even foxier in person.
你没跟我说你有孩子呢
You didn't tell me that you had kids.
这是戴尔  本  莎拉  丹尼斯和加里
This is Dale, Ben, Sarah, Denise, and Gary.
-为了这个考试我复习了好久  -抱歉
- I studied my ass off for this test. - I'm sorry.
我的肝不好
I have this liver condition.
基本废了  医生说我需要一个新的
Pretty much kicked. They say I need a new one.
可怎么从来没有印第安人需要肝移植的
I never hear of an Indian getting a liver transplant.
我们用汗蒸小屋来治病
We use a sweat lodge.
它能净化你的肝脏  你的脾脏  感觉非常好
Cleans your liver, your spleen, and it's a real high.
弗兰克
Frank?
你俩怎么好上的
How'd you guys start getting it on?
我灌醉了他  差点在帐篷里上了他
I got him drunk and almost fucked him in a tent.
我有时是有一点狂野
I can get a little wild.
我永远不会告诉他的  这事根本没发生过
I'm not telling him. This did not happen.
你跟我一样爽
You got off on it as much as I did.
-该死  -搞什么
- God damn it! - What?
-麦克  我不知道他说了什...  -别说了  走吧
- Mike, I don't know what he-- - Please, just go.
你他妈来这里干什么
What the fuck are you doing here?
通过道歉的方式  派对开始
By way of apologizing. Now it's a party.
菲奥娜
Fiona!
他没呼吸了
He's not breathing!
天呐
Oh, my god!
-他脸上的是什么  -天呐
- What's on his face? - Oh, my god.
-他吸了我的可卡因  -菲奥娜是哪位
- He got into my coke. - Who's Fiona?
-是我  -菲奥娜·加拉格
- That's me. - Fiona Gallagher...
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
但是你所说的一切  都将成为呈堂证供
Anything you say can and will be used against you in a court of law.
无耻家庭
第四季第六集
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译：  扎克不渣   重案组李Sir   企鹅三星带花   君君
■
翻译：  青椒    爱卿遛小鸟    拉图    ztonyy
时间轴：  吉吉    芝麻园子    aaaBao
■
校对：  落
后期： 孤帆          总监： 落
■
看摄像头
Look at the camera.
警察可能要先带她去六局备案
They probably took her to district 6 for booking.
嫌犯在被转到郡里之前都待在那个地方
That's where they usually take you before they transfer you to county.
她需要一名律师
She's gonna need a lawyer.
想让我们帮忙联系什么人吗
You got anybody you want us to call?
利普
Lip?
你们有律师吗
Is there a lawyer you want us to use?
几年前我因为醉驾的事
I used a guy on Calumet a couple years ago
请过一个卡鲁梅市的律师
for that D.U.I. thing I had, you know?
他身上总有一股脏洗碗布的臭味
He smells like dirty dish towels,
在他身边你得用嘴呼吸才行
but if you breathe through your mouth, it's bearable.
-菲奥娜·加拉格  -我是菲利普·加拉格
- Fiona gallagher? - Philip gallagher.
-菲奥娜在这里吗  -不在
- Is Fiona here? - No.
-她会过来吗  -不会  短期内不行
- Will she be back? - No, not soon.
我是利亚姆的哥哥
I'm--I'm Liam's brother.
那有没有其他家长或法定监护人在这里呢
Is there another parent or legal guardian available?
没有  利亚姆他不会有事吧
No. Is Liam gonna be okay?
抱歉  必须要有一名能担责的成人在场...
I'm sorry. I really need a responsible adult present--
听着  我妈是个有躁郁症的吸毒者
Look, my mom's a bipolar drug addict
她几年前就跟我们分开了
who split years ago,
而我爸是个醉汉
and my dad's a drunk,
警察又刚把菲奥娜铐到监狱去了
and the cops just hauled Fiona off to jail, okay?
我是你现在唯一可以找到的
Look, I'm the only thing that passes for a responsible adult
能担责的成人了  利亚姆现在怎么样了
that you're gonna find. Now, how is Liam?
你弟弟被送来时可卡因中毒
Your brother came in with acute cocaine toxicity--
已经神志不清  出现幻觉  且心率骤升有生命危险
disoriented, hallucinating, and with a dangerously elevated heart rate.
我们已经给他注射纳洛酮和苯二氮
He's on naloxone for his altered mental status
来分别缓解神志不清和癫痫的症状
and benzodiazepine to control his seizures.
癫痫
Seizures?
我们正在监测他的体温
We're monitoring his temperature,
心率和血糖指数
his heart rate, and his glucose levels,
总算都开始稳定下来了
but he has started to settle down.
-我们可以看他吗  -抱歉不行
- Can we see him? - I'm sorry.
只有年满18岁的直系亲属
Only immediate family members over 18
可以进入儿科重症监护室
are allowed in the PICU.
去吧  我们在这里陪着卡尔和小黛
Go. We'll stay here with Carl and Debs.
你可以摸摸他
You can touch him.
他为什么被绑着
Why is he, uh, tied down?
因为他之前焦躁不安甚至伤害自己
He was agitated and hurting himself.
这是过量吸食可卡因的常见症状
It's not unusual in cocaine overdoses.
那他会没事吗
Is he gonna be okay?
现在还说不准
Well, it's early yet,
但过量吸食可卡因通常不会致命
but cocaine overdoses aren't usually fatal.
他确实犯过几次癫痫
He did have several seizures,
这种情况会导致智力下降
and that can lead to intellectual decline.
会损伤大脑吗
Brain damage?
可能会导致学习和语言障碍
Learning and language problems,
以及情绪和行为障碍
emotional and behavioral disorders.
正在发育的大脑是很脆弱的
The developing brain is delicate.
你最好咨询儿科神经学家
You're gonna need to consult with a pediatric neurologist
看是否造成任何可能的长远损伤
to monitor any possible long-term deficits.
你的弟弟...他是个小硬汉
Look, your little brother is a-- he's a tough guy.
生命力很顽强
He's strong.
我相信他会痊愈的
If I was a betting woman, my money would be on a full recovery.
没事了  我在这里
It's okay. Here we go.
运输车来了  女士们
Transport van is here. Ladies.
我们这是要去哪里
Where are we going?
去4局办手续
Division 4 for processing.
-举起手来  -我弟弟在医院
- Put your hands up. - My brother's in the hospital.
我要打个电话问问他情况如何
I-I need to make a call and find out how he's doing.
过去之后就能打了
You'll have access to a phone after intake at division 4.
好了吗  走吧  快点
Set? Let's go. Come on.
有新消息吗
Anything new?
我们把小黛和卡尔弄去睡了  小维会陪在他们身边
We got Deb and Carl into bed. V is gonna stay with them.
我已经联系过警察那边了
And I got a hold of the cops.
他们要把菲奥娜转移到女子监狱
They're moving Fiona to women's county.
我们可以在她被提讯的地方见到她
We can catch up to her over there for her arraignment.
你在填什么
What's that?
许可文书
It's admissions paperwork.
"保险"  没有
"Insurance"? None.
"雇主"  没有
"Employer"? None.
"信用卡号"  没有
"Credit card number"? None.
老天
Jesus.
也许他们会让我们去自助餐厅洗盘子
Maybe they'll let us wash dishes in the cafeteria.
不会的  他们会治好他的
No, fuck that. They got to treat him.
他们不至于因为你们没钱
They're not gonna kick a sick toddler to the curb
就把一个生病的孩子踢到路边不管的
'cause he doesn't have a gold card.
可他们还是会派讨债公司的人过来的
That doesn't mean they're not gonna send a collection agency our way.
怎么  你还担心他们会弄烂你的信用等级
What, you're worried they're gonna fuck up your credit rating?
菲奥娜的保释听证会就在今天中午
Fiona's bail hearing is around noon sometime.
我给那个律师留言了
I left a message with that lawyer.
-不要  -什么不要
- No. - No, what?
那个律师不收钱吗
Uh, lawyer work for free?
我和小维可以先帮你们垫着
V and I can front you some cash.
怎么  帮我们垫点钱
What, front us some cash?
好像我们能还你似的
Like we're ever gonna be able to pay you back?
-她需要一位律师  -她会有的
- She needs a lawyer. - And she'll get one.
警局会给她派一位的
The P.D.'s office will handle it.
你他妈开玩笑吧
Are you fucking kidding me?
一个刚从法律学院毕业的
An overworked public defender straight out of law school
同时要处理几百个案件的公设辩护律师
with a couple hundred cases?
我觉得挺好
Works for me.
那是个意外  利普
It was an accident, Lip.
你说是就是吧
If you say so.
这事儿很严重  孩子
This is some heavy shit, kid.
一个3岁的孩子服用非法毒品
Illegal drugs, a three-year-old?
她可能要坐牢坐很久
She might end up doing some serious time.
她可是家人
She's family.
快5点了
It's almost 5:00.
3小时后我有量子物理考试
I've got a quantum physics quiz in three hours.
看来是赶不上了
Guess I'm gonna miss it, huh?
-你跟你妈长得真像  -什么
- You look like your mother. - What?
-她特别漂亮  -天呐  你差点死了
- She was a real looker. - Oh, my God. We almost lost you.
-她还那么漂亮吗  -我妈吗
- She still a knockout? - My mom?
不是了
Not so much.
时间是把杀猪刀啊
Life hasn't been kind.
她得上了糖尿病  截了一只脚
Diabetes-- lost a foot.
之前患上了乳腺癌  做双乳切除术
Breast cancer before that-- double mastectomy.
两个都切掉了
Both of 'em, huh?
之后重塑了
They rebuilt them.
也很不错
Did a good job too.
她之前总是抱怨胸部太小了
She was always complaining out how she was a little small up there,
所以她让医生增加了罩杯
so she had the doc add a couple bra sizes.
小  我不记得小来着
Small? I don't remember that.
但是乳头没能重塑
Couldn't rebuild the nipples, though,
所以她就纹了一对儿
so she had them tattooed on.
也很不错
Did a pretty good job too--
近看也很真
Even up close.
-看看谁清醒了  -他刚醒
- Look who's conscious. - He just woke up.
这是扎伯医生  他救了你的命
This is Dr. Zabel. He saved your life.
尽力而为  感觉怎么样  弗兰克
Well, temporarily at best. How you feeling, Frank?
相当糟  我认识你吗
Shitty. Do I know you?
当然  我们是老朋友了
Sure. We're old friends.
根据你冗长的病史
According to your extensive medical history,
这是你第56次来我们这个救死扶伤之地了
this is your 56th visit to our hallowed hall of healing.
你在这儿都成传奇了  弗兰克
You're a legend around here, Frank.
再多来两次  你就赢了斯坦
Two more visits, you'll pass Sterno Stan
成为我们最荣誉的常客了
as our most decorated frequent flyer.
我记得你
I remember you.
我吸毒最嗨的那次被你糟蹋了
You fucked up my best high ever.
我可真傻
Silly me.
早知道我就不用纳络酮  让你吸毒过量好了
I should have skipped the narcan, let you OD.
我要是让你被呕吐物呛死的话
I suspect our billing department would have sent me on a carnival cruise
我们的财务部门会好好奖励我的
if I just let you choke to death on your own vomit.
不  没事的
No, I was fine.
我又不是第一次那么干  没问题的
I've done five speedballs before, no problem-o.
你女儿跟我说
Now, according to your daughter here,
你在蒸汗屋里晕倒了
you passed out in a sweat lodge?
我就不问这大冬天的你在芝加哥
Beyond the obvious question of where you found a sweat lodge
是怎么找到一个汗蒸屋的
in the city of Chicago in the middle of winter,
你到底是怎么想的
what in God's name were you thinking?
肝脏功能衰竭了  没时间移植了
Liver's giving out, no time to get a new one.
印第安人的法子能把酒精从肝脏蒸出来
Indians sweat the alcohol out and live forever.
我知道西医
I realize western medicine
没有给你别的选择  弗兰克
isn't offering you many alternatives, Frank,
但是这么瞎弄会让你死得更快
but all that holistic crap will kill you faster.
你酗酒多久了
How long you been a drinker?
12岁开始
Started when I was 12.
然后就再也没清醒过
Never breathed a sober breath since,
直到这个破肝不干活了
till this damn liver quit doing its job.
干什么活
What job is that?
消化我每天给它补充的过量酒精
Processing the copious amounts of alcohol I send its way daily.
如果有一个反戒酒协会
If there were an anti-A.A.,
我会有个40年的酗酒奖章在我口袋里叮当响
I'd have a 40-year drunk chip rattling around in my pocket.
鉴于你这40年来
Given your four decades of stumble-down,
对酒精的不离不弃
hammered-in-the-gutter commitment to pro-level alcoholism...
谢谢
Thank you.
我觉得你应该给你的肝在博卡买套公寓
I think you owe your liver a condo in Boca
还有推圆盘游戏桌
and some shuffleboard.
你知道你快死了  对吧
You know you're dying, right?
我们都会死  医生
We're all dying, doc.
你会很快
Soon?
不会
Nope.
我还没准备死呢
Not ready to punch my ticket yet.
我还有10年的好日子
I got a good ten years left.
只要给我这老肝几个月的时间修复一下
Just got to give this old liver a couple of months to rejuvenate,
-就能重回往日光辉  -还有多长时间
- get its mojo back. - How soon?
不多了
Very soon.
需要开始准备后事那么快
"Order the flowers and decide between an urn or a casket" soon.
不可能的  医生
Not gonna happen, doc.
你不知道我们加拉格家的人
You don't know us Gallaghers.
我们恢复力强
We're resilient.
你有肝硬化
You have cirrhosis--
是长期病变的结果
the result of chronic progressive liver disease.
你正在丧失了排泄功能
You're losing excretory function.
出现了腹水  静脉出血
You've developed ascites, variceal hemorrhages,
肝性脑病  还有肾损害的症状
hepatic encephalopathy, and renal impairment.
大限将至  弗兰克
Time's up, Frank.
我们还能做什么吗
Is there anything else we can do?
剩下的日子让他舒服一些
Make him comfortable.
临终关怀院是个不错的选择
Hospice is an excellent option.
我猜费用会是个问题
I assume cost is an issue.
这附近有几家不错的
There are several nice ones around
愿意接收穷人
that accept the indigent--
属于宗教机构的
Run by religious orders,
但是能在最后的日子里
but well worth a couple choruses of Amazing Grace
听一听《奇异恩典》也值得了
To have your last days be someplace nice.
很高兴认识你  弗兰克
Pleasure knowing you, Frank.
祝你好运
Good luck.
你也是  医生
Back at you, doc.
菲奥娜·加拉格
Fiona Gallagher?
是的
Yes?
-患有疾病吗  -没有
- Any medical issues? - No.
糖尿病  肺结核  艾滋病  食物过敏
Diabetes? Tuberculosis? H.I.V.? Food allergies?
对什么上瘾吗
You hooked on anything--
药物依赖什么的
drug dependencies we should know about?
有在服药吗
What about medications?
-有服用处方药吗  -没有
- You taking any prescription meds? - No.
-请交出私人物品  -什么
- Personal items, please. - What?
手表  戒指  手镯  耳环
Watch, rings, bracelets, earrings,
钱包  钱
wallet, money.
钥匙  其他各类穿孔首饰
Keys, any other piercings,
以及口袋里的所有物品
everything in your pockets.
我的弟弟在医院里
My brother's in the hospital.
我得打个电话  得知他是否平安
I need to make a call, find out how he's doing.
-手臂伸过来  -求你了  我能打个电话
- Arm, please. - Please, can I make a call
-了解我弟弟的情况吗  -名字没错吧
- and find out how my brother's doing? - That you?
在这里签字以证明这是你给我的物品
Sign here to acknowledge these are the possessions you gave me.
沿大厅直走右转  准备更衣
Down the hall to the right and strip.
走吧
Let's go.
这里
In there.
把衣服放进袋子里
Clothes in the bag.
还有内衣
Underwear too.
手抬起来
Arms up.
张开嘴巴
Open your mouth.
翻开上嘴唇
Flip up the top lip.
翻开下嘴唇
Flip the bottom.
舌头伸起来
Lift up your tongue.
检查脚底
Soles of your feet.
另一只脚
Mm-hmm. The other one.
请弯下腰来
Bend over for me, please.
咳嗽
Cough.
换上囚服
Put on the uniform.
我现在能打电话了吗
Can I get my call now, please?
换上囚服
Get in your uniform.
走吧
Let's go.
他们还在睡吗
They still sleeping?
是的  利亚姆怎么样
Yeah. Liam?
还是一样  利普留下来了
Same. Lip stayed.
有事他会打过来的
He's gonna call if anything changes.
来些咖啡吗
You want some coffee?
我们要不要叫他们起来上学
Should we be getting them ready for school?
他们两点钟才上床
They didn't get to bed till 2:00.
我都不记得当时看到过利亚姆了  你呢
I don't even remember seeing Liam, do you?
难不成他一直在楼下  我却没注意到他
Was he down here the whole time, and I just didn't notice him?
我  我不知道
I-I don't know.
这可是加拉格家的派对
It was a Gallagher pop-up party.
酒如泉涌
Booze was flowing.
人多耳杂
Noise was noisy.
场面乱得一塌糊涂
There was a lot of shit going on.
我应该注意到他的  应该留个神的
I should've noticed him, kept an eye on him.
利亚姆不是我们的孩子
It's not our kid.
看好他不是我们的义务
It's not our job to watch him.
怎么不是我们的义务
It is our job.
利普人在大学  伊恩又不见人影
With Lip off at college and Ian running away,
菲奥娜不可能一个人看好这么多孩子
Fiona can't keep track of these kids all by herself.
我并不是说这是她的错
Look, I'm not saying it's her fault.
我的意思是这同样不是我们的错
I'm just saying that it's not ours either.
这件事不是任何人的错  天有不测风云
It's nobody's. Shit happens.
那我们的孩子出事了怎么办
What's gonna happen with our babies?
他们不会有事的  我们会保证他们的安全
They're gonna be fine. We're gonna keep 'em safe.
他们将幸福快乐地长大
They're gonna grow up happy and smart
到时候替公牛队打球
and play for the Bulls.
其中一个还会被选为总统
One of 'em's gonna be elected president.
-美国总统吗  -当然了  怎么不会
- Of the United States? - Hell, yeah. Why not?
我们不已经选了一个起着中东独裁者名字的
We already elected a skinny half-black Muslim dude
精瘦的黑白混血穆斯林当总统了吗
named after a towel-head dictator.
早上好  沙利班先生
Good morning, Mr. Shaliban.
这是汗蒸小屋
It's a sweat lodge.
它对排毒很有帮助
It's great for getting rid of toxins.
过些时候把你妈妈带过来  我们会加热好的
Yeah, bring your mom by later. We'll heat it up.
这对她的肺气肿一定会有帮助
I'm sure it'll help her emphysema.
祝你有个美好的一天  沙利班先生
Okay, have a good day, Mr. Shaliban.
恶臭风
Stinking wind!
独眼蛇  奔翔
One-eyed snake! Runs with poo!
早餐好了
Breakfast!
这是他们胡编的名字  你知道吧
You knww that's not their real names, right?
这些都是他们告诉我的
It's the names they gave me.
今天早上感觉怎么样
How are you feeling this morning?
有些酸痛
A little sore.
感觉被侵犯  不过是好的那种
Violated, but in a good way.
就跟骑了一天的马差不多
Nothing I haven't felt after spending a day on the saddle.
"大家好"用梅诺米尼语
How do you say, um, "Hello, everyone"
怎么说
in Menominee?
希望你们都饿了
I hope you're hungry!
我做了蓝玉米饼和黑蔗糖浆
I've got, um, nokake pancakes and molasses syrup!
虽然很不舍  但是我们
So we're gonna have to be heading back
今天就要回保留地了
to the reservation today, sad to say.
什么  这么快
What? Already?
他们要上学了
Their education beckons.
离这里有多远
How far is it?
梅诺米尼吗  大概一个半小时  看交通
Menominee? About 90 minutes, depending on the traffic.
有巴特沃斯夫人牌的糖浆吗
Got any Mrs. Butterworth's?
老实吃饭  谢谢别人
Eat and say thank you.
我应该要花几周的时间找我姐姐
It should only be a couple weeks while I track down my sister.
她可能又跑到里诺市去赌博了
She's probably out in Reno again.
小木屋牌枫叶糖浆呢
Log Cabin maple?
老实吃饭
Eat it!
如果你喜欢的话
I have some homemade huckleberry jam
我这里有些自制的越橘酱
if you'd prefer.
这些就好了  他们不是正在吃吗
They're good. They're eating.
好吧
Okay.
我  我在想
I was--I was thinking, well...
也许我能来保留地来看你们
maybe I could come visit you on the reservation.
我还从来没去过呢
I've never been.
当然可以  你可以和我们一起住
Sure. Why not? You can stay with us.
我们有很多房间
We have plenty of room.
你们有广阔的农田和牧场吗
Do you have a lot of land for farming and agriculture?
我们住在赌场后面的活动板房里
We live in a double-wide behind the casino.
挺不错的
Oh, that sounds nice.
赌场里有一个带滑梯的泳池
Casino has a pool with a slide.
还有一个卡丁车赛道
And a go-kart track.
多吃饭  少说话
Less talking, more eating, please.
好了
There you go.
要我帮你吗
Want some help with that?
本次受话付费电话来自
You have a collect call
库克郡监狱  拨号人
from the Cook County jail from...
菲奥娜·加拉格
Fiona Gallagher.
接听本次通话  请按井号键
To accept this call, press pound.
To accept this call, press pound,
其他服务请按零
or press zero for more options.
请注意  来自这所机构的所有通话内容
Please be aware that all calls from this facility
都会被执法部门监听并录音
Are recorded and monitored by law enforcement authorities.
喂
Hello?
利普
Lip?
他怎么样了
How is he?
利亚姆吗
Liam?
是的  利亚姆  天啊
Yes, Liam. Jesus!
利普
Lip?
他还活着
He's alive.
他现在在儿科重症监护室
He's in the pediatric intensive care unit.
但他会没事的对吗
but he's gonna be okay?
当然了
Sure.
他被绑起来了  怕他再抓伤自己
Yeah, he's strapped down, 'cause he was hurting himself.
吃了一堆药  还在打点滴
He's on a ton of drugs and an I.V.
并很可能留下永久性脑损伤
And could have permanent brain damage,
但他会活下去的
But he's gonna live.
你还在听吗
Are you still there?
是的  我还在听
Yeah, I'm here.
求你了  求你了
Please, please...
-加拉格先生  -请你告诉他
- Mr. Gallagher? - Please, tell him that--
我得挂了
Got to go.
请你告诉他我爱他  好吗
Please tell him that I love him, okay?
我真的很抱歉  求你了
And I'm so, so sorry. Please?
求你了  利普
Please? Lip?
利普
Lip!
他的心率和血压
So his heart rate and his blood pressure
都已经回归正常了
Have returned to normal,
血糖水平也稳定下来了
And his glucose levels have stabilized.
那意味着我们可以把他移到楼下的
That means we're gonna move him downstairs
普通儿科病房了
To a bed in the general pediatrics ward
不过要先等那边有床位空出来
As soon as one becomes available.
-明白吗  -好的
- Okay? - Good.
他应该再过个  大约一两天
He should be ready to be discharged then
就可以出院了
In, like, I don't know, a day or two.
那太好了
Good. That's good.
菲利普  这位是马特洛克小姐
Uh, Philip, this is Ms. Matlock.
她是社会服务部门的
She's from social services.
我叫安  加拉格先生
Anne. Mr. Gallagher.
你姐姐是你弟弟的法定监护人吗
Your sister is your brother's legal guardian?
包括我父亲一起
Along with my father, yeah.
利亚姆出事时  你父亲在家吗
Was your father at home when the incident with Liam occurred?
不  不  他不在
Uh, no, no, he wasn't there.
你知道你父亲在哪儿吗
Do you know where your father is?
不知道
No idea.
他不住在家里吗
He doesn't live in the home?
不  我在外上大学  所以我不知道
No, I've been away at college, so I-I don't know.
你知道我们在哪儿可以找到他吗
Do you know where we can find him?
不知道
No.
你姐姐现在被警方拘留了吗
And your sister is in police custody?
你得在利亚姆出院前
You're gonna need to find your father
找到你父亲
Before Liam is ready to be released,
否则我们只能将他收入寄养系统了
Or we're gonna have to place him into foster care.
我可以做他的监护人吗
Can I take responsibility for him?
我成年了  18岁了
I'm--I'm an adult, 18.
你在上大学  对吧
You're away at college, right?
是的  但我可以退学的  我可以照顾他
Uh, yeah, but I'll--I'll quit. You know, I can take him.
你可以向法庭请愿
You can petition the court,
但那需要时间
But that takes time.
如果你不希望你弟弟被送去寄养
Your father is the quicker solution
找到你父亲才是解决问题的快速方法
If you want to keep your brother out of foster care,
即使是暂时解决也行
Even temporarily.
好吧
Okay.
你想去看看他吗
Would you like to see him?
-是啊  -好的
- Yes. - Okay.
嘿  小家伙
Hey, buddy.
看我把谁带来了
Look who I brought.
嘿  你还好吗  小家伙
Hey, how you doing? Hi!
嗨  小猴崽
Hi, monkey man!
你没事了
You're okay.
你至少该去看一眼啊
You should at least take a look.
不用了  谢谢
No, thank you.
可能很不错呢
Could be nice.
一帮癌症病人尖叫着索要吗啡
A bunch of cancer patients screaming for morphine...
肿瘤正缓慢地侵蚀他们的骨头
As tumors slowly break their bones,
一些修女往那些倒霉蛋身上洒圣水
Some nun sprinkling the poor fuckers with holy water?
其中一个是卫理公会派的
One of them was the methodists.
-我觉得那里是没有修女的  -没兴趣
- I don't think they have nuns. - Not interested.
你之前为什么没问过我关于我妈的事
Why haven't you asked me about my mom before?
-什么  -你以前从没向我问起过她
- What? - You never asked me about her.
那是很早以前的事了
That was a long time ago.
你想见见她吗
You want to meet her?
-你跟她说了我的事吗  -还没有
- Did you tell her about me? - Not yet.
她很可能也不会对你说起我
Probably just as well.
我们当时分得很难堪
We didn't exactly part on good terms.
怎么会那样
How come?
她跟我说她怀孕了  我让她扔掉我的号码
She told me she was pregnant, I told her to lose my number.
为什么
Why?
什么为什么
Why what?
你为什么不想做我的父亲
Why didn't you want to be my dad?
我们当时都很年轻  情况很复杂
We were young. It was complicated.
怎么个复杂法
Complicated how?
她想把你生下来
She wanted to keep you.
你当时想让她去堕胎吗
Y-you wanted her to get an abortion?
现在我很开心她没有去堕
Well, now I'm glad that she didn't,
但当时我就是那么想的
But at the time, hell, yes.
我们都不怎么认识对方
We barely knew each other.
她跟我说你们相爱了
She told me you two were in love!
其实并没有那么浪漫啦
Well, it wasn't quite that romantic.
我们是在派对上认识的  服用了太多迷幻剂
We met at a party, did too much peyote,
我把她扑倒在了约翰尼·沃什家地下室的烘干机上
And I bent her over a dryer in Johnny Walsh's basement.
烘干机
A dryer?
我记得当时里面好像有双网球鞋
I remember there was a tennis shoe
或什么的  不断地发出撞击声
Or something in there-kept thumping.
我就按照那个节奏干你妈
I banged your mom to the rhythm of the thing.
好了  萨咪  等等  等等
Okay, Sammi, wait! Wai--loo--oh.
我们确实不是听着音乐  在浪漫烛光中做爱的
It wasn't candles and Barry White on the stereo.
谁在乎呢
Who cares?
那一夜的种子  诞生出了独一无二的美丽之物
Something incredibly beautiful and special came out of it...
就是你
You.
至少你去看一眼吧
Will you at least take a look?
看什么
At what?
临终关怀院
The hospice places!
我他妈为什么要去
Oh, for christ's sake, why?
求你了
Please.
不去
No.
好吧
Okay!
我去
Okay.
我去就是了
I'll go.
等等  你说你妈平胸吗
Wait. "Small-breasted," you said?
可我记得干洗机上的那位身材很好啊
I could have sworn the girl I bent over the dryer had a nice set.
也许我看洛史都华音乐会时
Maybe your mom was the chick in the porta-potty
在厕所里上的那位才是你妈
at the Rod Stewart concert.
加拉格
Gallagher!
左转
Here to your left.
菲奥娜·加拉格
Fiona gallagher?
我是玛丽亚·薇达尔
Maria Vidal.
今天的提审我将担任你的辩护律师
I'll be your public defender for today's arraignment.
欢迎来到我的办公室
Please, welcome to my office.
-以前经历过这类事吗  -没有
- You been through this before? - No.
好吧  整个流程大概需要90秒
All right, it's gonna take all of about 90 seconds.
法官会宣读控诉罪名
The judge is gonna read the charges.
然后会询问你的请求  你说"我无罪"
He's gonna ask you how you plea. You say, "Not guilty."
然后他会定个保释金额
Then he's gonna set a bail amount.
并宣布初审听证会的时间
Then he'll give us a preliminary hearing date.
交了保释金  你就可以出去了
You post the bond, and you get the hell out of here.
这是个意外
It was an accident.
我根本不知道我弟弟还在楼下...
I had no idea that my brother was still downstair--
菲奥娜  你叫菲奥娜吧
Fiona. Fiona, right?
这个之后再谈
That's a conversation for later.
现在  我们得先去见法官
Right now we have to get you in front of the judge.
你准备好了吗
Are you ready?
很好
Good.
加拉格  我们里面见
Gallagher, I'll see you inside.
皮特  你好吗
Hi, Pete. How you doing?
直走
Straight ahead.
菲奥娜·加拉格
Fiona Gallagher.
S6-974356号案件
Case s6-974356.
-律师都来了吗  -是的  法官阁下
- Is counsel present? - Yes, your honor.
请宣读控诉罪名
Read the charges.
拥有受管制药物
Possession of a controlled substance,
属于四级重罪
a class 4 felony
违反了伊利诺斯州刑法有关规定
under 720 Illinois Criminal Statute 570.1,
轻率行为危害儿童
and child endangerment,
违反了伊利诺斯州刑法第十二章第三节第五条
a violation of the reckless conduct code 720 ILCS 5 section 12c-5,
为三级重罪
a class 3 felony.
被告是否进行控辩
How does the defendant plead?
加拉格女士
Miss Gallagher?
我无罪  法官阁下
Not guilty, your honor.
辩护律师要求在保释后
Defense requests the accused be released
对被告进行释放
on her own recognizance.
幼童吸食可卡因过量
Cocaine overdose in a toddler?
那孩子还在重症病房呢
The child is still in intensive care.
保释金为十万美金
Bail is set at $100,000.
请跟工作人员确定初审日期
Check with the clerk to get a preliminary hearing date.
-什么  -下一位
- What? - Next.
杰克森  案件号S4-264296
Jackson, s4-264296.
直走
All right, straight down.
左转
Left.
-请等一下  -怎么
- Excuse me! - Yes!
我们是菲奥娜·加拉格的家人
We're Fiona Gallagher's family.
-所以呢  -十万美金
- Okay. - $100,000?
她又不是杀了人  又肢解
She didn't carve some dude up
还把尸体扔进冰箱
and stuff his parts in the freezer!
你们不用非得凑够十万
You don't have to put up $100,000.
县监狱只要保释金的10%
County only requires 10% for the bond.
一万吗
10 grand?
也接受同等价值的物品  比如房子或车
They accept collateral of equal value--a house, a car.
初审的时候我可以试着要求降低金额
I can try to get it reduced at her preliminary hearing.
如果受害者恢复了...
If the victim recovers...
-利亚姆  -如果他恢复
- Liam. - Liam recovers,
法官也许会考虑降低保释金额
that could influence the judge to lower her bail.
我先走了
Got to go.
-一万美金  -别想了  没有
- $10,000? - Forget it. We don't have it.
那也不能留她在监狱里啊
We can't just leave her in jail.
-我们付不起保释金  小黛  -可以攒啊
- We don't have the money, Debs. - We can raise it.
-可以卖东西  -行了  我操
- We can sell stuff-- - No! Christ!
别管了行吗  小黛
Just drop it! Fuck, debs!
黛比
Debbie!
说得真好  你个混蛋
Smooth, asshole. Smooth.
得先找到弗兰克
Look, we got to find Frank,
不然利亚姆要被送去寄养家庭了
or they're gonna put Liam into foster care.
我操
Shit.
卡尔  你回医院去  好吗
Carl, I want you to go back to the hospital, all right?
陪着利亚姆  有新情况随时通知我们
Stay with Liam, keep us updated on how he's doing.
我已经回家看过了  他不在
Look, I already tried the house. He wasn't there.
又得到处找他去了
All right, you up for another round of "Where the fuck's Frank?"
好  没问题
Yeah, sure.
也许在希拉家的汗蒸小屋里
Could be in Sheila's sweat lodge.
什么东西
Her what?
或者是杂货店旁边那女人的房车里
Or over at that chick's trailer by the save-a-lot.
她直接上公交了  我没追到
She hopped a bus before I could catch her.
她在气头上  气消就回去了
She's upset. She'll just go home.
还用你说
Wonder why.
怎么  怪我吼她吗
What? Me yelling at her?
你觉得最近发生的这些事里
You think that's the most traumatic thing
我吼她算是最严重的吗
that's happened to her in the last 18 hours?
行了  大家出发吧
Let's just go see if we can find
看看我们家那位负责任的爹
whatever gutter our responsible adult of a father
又死到哪里去了
has crawled into this time.
临终关怀是为重病人士提供的
Hospice is a philosophy of care
一种人性化照顾理念
for those faced with a life-limiting illness.
我们注重生命的质量
We emphasize quality of life.
我们并不加快或延缓死亡的发生
And we neither hasten nor postpone death
而是会为客人
while still supporting
在情感上  身体上  心灵上
the emotional, physical, spiritual,
提供实际性帮助和服务
and practical needs of our guests.
真是太好了  不是吗  爸爸
It is so nice. Isn't it nice, dad?
请跟我来
Follow me.
我们有社工
We have medical social workers.
理疗员还有按摩师
We have physical therapists, music and massage therapists,
丧亲心理咨询师
bereavement specialists,
护士  当然还有临终忏悔的牧师
Nurses, and, of course, there's a priest on duty
全天候待命
at all times for the final hours.
每个人都有自己的房间
Everyone has their own room.
欢迎你从家里带私人物品来这儿
And you're welcome to bring personal items from home
让你感觉更舒服
to make you feel more comfortable.
我们认为抚摸是临终疗护
We feel that touch is a very important part
非常重要的部分
of our end-of-life therapies.
你好  格特鲁
Hi, Gertrude,
特西先生
Mr. Tashegian.
胰腺癌晚期
End-stage pancreatic cancer.
病来如山倒
Came on fast.
六周前还在上游泳课呢
Six weeks ago, he was swimming laps at the "Y".
听起来好像梅兰妮和麦考密克太太那边的活动开始了
Oh! Sounds like Melanie's with Mrs. McCormick!
*奇异恩典*
*Amazing grace*
她的嗓音是不是很棒
Doesn't she have a marvelous voice?
跑遍全球为人人至上组织[非营利性组织]领唱
Traveled the world singing lead for "Up with people".
脑肿瘤
Brain tumor.
麦考密克太太已经昏迷好几周了
Mrs. McCormick's been comatose for weeks,
但是音乐好像能慰藉她
but the music seems to soothe her.
你怎么知道
How can you tell?
她听了音乐就不怎么呻吟了
She doesn't moan so much.
神父  谢谢你这么快赶来
Oh, father, thanks for coming so quickly.
约巴先生就在走廊尽头
Mr. Jobar, end of the hall.
请快一点  他时间不多了
Please hurry. He doesn't have much time.
医院说你们接收贫困人群
The hospital said you take people with limited means.
是的  收入有限的人
Oh, yes, we work with medicare,
可以用医疗保险或医疗补助
medicaid, the indigent.
太棒了
Oh, that's great.
是不是很棒  爸
Isn't that great, dad?
爸
Dad?
爸  你去哪
Dad? Where are you going?
我不能待在这座死亡之屋里
I can't be in that house of horrors!
-爸  别这样  -死亡商人
- Oh, dad, please! - Merchants of death.
她还不如穿件黑色斗篷
She might as well be wearing a black cloak
-手持镰刀呢  -说什么傻话啊
- and carrying a scythe. - That's silly!
-他们人很好  -多年来他们在别人睡梦中
- They seem nice. - They murder people in their sleep,
杀死他们  然后兑现他们的医疗补助支票
cash their medicaid checks for years!
爸  别这样  你这是无理取闹
Dad, come on! You're being ridiculous!
我不能待在那里  我不能
I can't be in that place! I can't--
我不能  我  我不能
I can't--I ca--I can't!
-行吗  -行吧
- Okay? - Okay.
我做不到
I can't!
我只想回家
I-I just want to go home.
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay, okay.
我带你回家
I'll take you home.
利亚姆住院了
liam's in the hospital.
他差点死了  菲奥娜在牢里
He almost died, and Fiona's in jail.
弗兰克  你在吗
Frank! Frank, you in there?
你确定是这辆车吗
Are you sure we got the right one?
卡尔说她就住这辆
Yeah, Carl said she was in this one.
弗兰克
Frank!
操
Shit.
会在艾莱柏酒吧吗
At the Alibi?
他戒酒以后就没去过了
He hasn't been around since he stopped drinking.
好吧  公园  桥洞  小巷
Okay, so parks, under bridges, alleys,
救济堂  停尸间
the--the missions, the morgue.
利普  这不是菲奥娜的错
Look, Lip, it wasn't Fiona's fault.
我们都在
We were all there.
都没看到利亚姆
Nobody saw Liam.
你知道的  对吧
You know that, right?
你怎么样
How you holding up?
还行
Okay.
你看起来不太好  像是毒瘾发作
You don't look good. You look strung out.
这儿有戒毒项目...
They got a rehab program in here--
美沙酮什么的
Methadone, whatever.
我不是瘾君子
I'm not a drug addict.
不是吗
No?
-不是  -那可卡因呢
- No. - Cocaine?
纯属偶然
That--that's not a regular thing.
昨天是我生日
Yesterday was my birthday.
那真是生日快乐了
Happy birthday.
我拿到了警方报告
I got a copy of the police report.
你跟医护人员说可卡因是你的
You told the paramedics it was your coke?
你能给医院打个电话
Can you call the hospital, please,
问问我弟现在怎么样吗
and find out how my brother's doing?
利亚姆  利亚姆·加拉格
Liam. Liam Gallagher.
我来这儿之前就打过了
I already did before coming over here.
他们说他好些了
They said he's doing better.
-不好意思  -没关系
- Sorry. Sorry. - It's okay.
没关系
It's okay.
你没事的
You're ok.
你准备告诉警方是谁把可卡因卖给你的吗
You prepared to tell the cops who sold you the coke?
什么
What?
如果你告诉他们一个名字
If you give 'em a name,
判决会就容易得多了
sentencing conference will go much easier.
什么意思
What does that mean?
地检办公室如无必要也不想
The D.A.'s Office is not gonna want to bring this to trial
让这案子走庭审
if they don't have to.
如果你合作  他们更愿意
They'll be much more open to negotiating probation
协商缓刑
if you cooperate.
给点谈判的筹码吧
Gives us a little bargaining chip to work with.
你从哪弄来的可卡因
Where'd you get the cocaine from?
如果是街角买的
If you bought it on a street corner,
别随便编一个人出来
don't just make up a guy.
浪费他们的时间可是会吃不了兜着走的
They will burn you for wasting their time.
我不是在街角买的
I didn't buy it on a street corner.
你愿意提供卖家姓名吗
Okay, so are you willing to provide them with a name?
不行
I can't do that.
你确定
Are you sure?
是的
Yes.
我们该上路了
Time to hit the concrete trail.
等下  我有...
Oh, wait! Hold on! I've got--
万一你们饿了  我为你们路上准备了些小吃
I got snacks for the road in case you get hungry.
罗杰  这是你的
Roger, that's for you.
恶臭风  这是你的
And, Stinking Wind, that's for you.
还有独眼蛇
And One-eyed Snake.
丹尼斯
Denise.
奔翔
And Runs With Poo.
当然还有莎拉
And, of course, Sarah.
你那份我加了特别的东西哦
That one has something special in it.
你真好  孩子们  该说什么
Very kind of you. What do you say, kids?
-谢谢  -谢谢您
- Thanks. - Thank you.
别担心
Don't worry.
里边是香蕉花生三明治
It's peanut butter and banana sandwiches
还有一些奇多和士力架
and Cheetos and some Snickers bars.
好吧  我们走吧
Okay, then, here we go.
好的  再见
Okay, good-bye!
再见
Good-bye!
拜拜
Bye!
Good-bye!
-拜拜  -拜拜
- Good-bye! - Bye.
你会爱斯基摩吻吗
Hey, do you know how to do an Eskimo kiss?
就像这样
Like this.
那你会蝴蝶吻吗
And do you know how to do a butterfly kiss?
就像这样
Like that.
过几周见  小野猫
See you in a couple weeks, wildcat.
好的  别忘记系安全带
okay, don't forget to buckle your seat belts!
好好照顾自己
Don't take any wooden nickels!
-宝贝  -宝贝
- Hey, baby. - Hey, babe.
-有进展吗  -没有
- Any luck? - No.
-弗兰克没来这里吗  -没有
- Frank never showed up here? - Nope.
-利普呢  -他先下车了
- Where's Lip? - Had me drop him off.
他过会回来找我们
He's gonna meet us at the house later.
这些是什么
What's all this?
我想把我们的财产
I was trying to figure where we were
理理清楚
cash- and asset-wise.
看看能不能凑出一万块钱
I was hoping we could scrape together 10 gran
-把菲奥娜弄出来  -然后呢
- to get Fiona out. - And?
还差得远
Not even close.
我给银行的罗尼打了个电话
I called Ronnie over at the bank
问问能不能贷点款
to see if we could borrow against the bar.
她说这得花上几周
She said it'll take weeks.
或许我们可以把卡车卖掉
Maybe we could sell the truck.
我查了二手汽车价目册
Yeah, I checked the blue book.
-只能卖四千块  -什么
- It's only worth 4 grand. - What?
我一万五买的
I paid 15,000.
那是在八年前
Yeah, eight years ago.
经典车型应该更贵才对
Then it should be a classic.
老天  没钱真要命
Christ, I am tired of being poor.
该死的
God damn it!
你们这些欠操的傻逼们
Fucking candy-assed motherfucking pussies!
给老子把手铐解开
Get these goddamn cuffs off!
老子不弄死你们
I'll kick your fucking ass!
你们这两个死基佬
You and your goddamn faggoty boyfriend!
一个顶个大龟头  一个扬着大臭逼
You pecker-neck bastards! You rotten motherfuckers!
狗屎不如的人渣  去你妈逼啊
Pig-ass pieces of shit! God damn you!
怎么了  他又捅人了
What, did he stab somebody again?
违反假释条例  尿检又没合格
Broke parole, failed another piss test.
靠  当初为什么把他放出来
Shit, why do they even bother to letting him out?
他不是早该进去蹲一辈了
He's got to be 50 or 60 swings past three strikes, right?
可能里边太挤了
It's overcrowding, I guess.
你是路过吗
You just passing by?
利亚姆住院了
Uh, Liam's in the hospital.
他不小心吃了菲奥娜的可卡因
Fiona left her coke out.
差点丢了命
He almost died.
靠  他怎么样了
Shit. Is he okay?
不知道
I don't know.
医生说"可能"  所以...
The doctors say "maybe," so...
菲奥娜肯定崩溃了
Fiona must be a wreck.
她被捕了
They arrested her--
私藏毒品  伤害儿童
um, possession and child endangerment.
操
Fuck.
伊恩回来了  你知道吧
Ian's back. You--you knew that, right?
你能去找他  顺便告诉他这边的情况吗
Think you could find him and tell him what happened?
当然
Sure.
曼迪
Yo, Mandy.
我得回去了
I got to go.
曼迪
Uh, Mandy.
谢谢你
Thank you.
弗兰克在吗
Is Frank here?
你妈在吗
Is your mom here?
还有其他人吗
Is anybody else?
刚把他哄睡
Just got him to sleep.
吃了四片奥施康定  两片安定  痛得要命
Took four oxys, two valium-- lots of pain.
-利普正在找你  -嘘  安静
- Lip's out looking for you. - Shh. Quiet.
四片奥施康定  两片安定
Four oxys and two "V"s?
你最好看看他还喘着气没
Better check if he's still breathing.
汗蒸管用吗
Did the sweat lodge help?
简直坑人
Death trap--
差点害死他
almost killed him.
他在急诊室躺了一晚
He spent the night in the E.R.
最好谁去把那东西拆掉
Someone has to tear that thing down
免得再害到别人
before it can try to claim another life.
老爸差点死掉
Dad almost died?
我不知道那个印第安疯子怎么会想到
I don't know what that crazy Indian thought he was doing
要搭个这棚子
building that thing,
但是这差点害了咱爸
but it almost took our father from us.
我要洗个澡
I need a shower.
帮帮忙  去看看恰奇饿了没
Be a dear, see if Chuckie's still hungry.
我给他买了些麦当劳  要是不够他吃的话
I bought him some Mcdonald's, but if he wants more,
就吃我的巨无霸
he can eat my big mac.
就在厨台上
It's on the kitchen counter.
卡尔
Carl!
嘿  卡尔
Yo, carl!
我靠
Shit.
我还以为你在医院呢
Hey, I thought you were supposed to be at the hospital?
护士让我回家
The nurses told me to go home.
弗兰克在楼上  吃了药睡着了
Frank's upstairs, knocked out on oxy.
在沙发上看黄片的是谁
Who's on the sofa watching porn?
-侄子  -什么
- Nephew. - A what?
护士说利亚姆正在"休养"
Nurses said Liam was "resting comfortably."
不是  这个侄子是谁
Wh--no, the--the nephew.
弗兰克说的
Oh, Frank says he is,
不过他可能是为了骗肝脏瞎掰的
But he could just be lying to get a liver.
楼上还有个新来的姐姐
We also got a new sister upstairs.
她在洗澡
She's in the shower.
老天
Jesus.
老弟  你从医院回来时候怎么不给我打电话
Hey, buddy, why didn't you call me before you left the hospital?
没电话  菲奥娜没收了
No phone-- Fiona confiscated it
就那次我偷韩国人腊肠被抓的时候
when I got busted for stealing Slim Jims from the Koreans.
好吧
Okay.
你凑到钱了吗
You got the money?
干什么
For what?
把菲奥娜弄出来的钱
Get Fiona out of jail.
没有
Oh, um... No.
我们就这么不管她了吗
So we're just gonna leave her there?
没办法
No choice.
为什么这世界如此操蛋
Why is the world so fucked up?
我也不知道
I don't know.
别人家也像我们家一样操蛋吗
Everybody's family this fucked up?
当然不是全部
Well, not everybody's,
但是大部分都挺操蛋
but a lot of them, yeah.
当然了  加拉格式的操蛋是无与伦比的
Of course, we're that extra-special gallagher kind of fucked up.
我要到医院去了
So, I'm gonna go back to the hospital.
明天记得去上学  听见没
Uh, school, tomorrow, okay?
黛比也得去
That means Debbie too.
她不在家
She's not here.
-黛比没回家吗  -没有
- Wait. Debbie didn't come home? - Nope.
一定要看住弗兰克
Hey, don't let Frank out of your sight, all right?
我们得靠他把利亚姆从医院接出来
We need him to get Liam out of the hospital.
她怎么不接电话
Fuck, why isn't she picking up?
黛比到底死哪儿去了
Damn it, where the hell is she?
嗨  你来啦
Hey, man.
谢谢你帮我把这个带过来
Oh, thanks for bringing this stuff.
没事儿  你弟弟怎么样了
Yeah, man, no problem. How's your brother?
他好多了
Oh, he's better. Yeah, good.
医生说他明天就能出院了
They think he can come home tomorrow, so...
太棒了兄弟  这太好了
Good, man. That's good.
我给你带了盒面
I brought you some ramen too.
太好了
Oh, great.
奥尔良烤鸡味的被我吃光了
I'm out of cajun chicken,
所以我给你带了盒烟熏火腿味的
so I brought you smoked ham.
谢谢  真的谢谢你
Oh, thanks. Really, man.
我得走了
Yeah. Well, I should get going.
阿曼达停车的位置是违章的
Amanda's double-parked out front,
而且她如果一个人呆久了容易发疯
and she gets kind of postal if you leave her alone too long.
行 你走吧
Right, yeah.
对了  莫斯把那篇康德的论文发下来了
Oh, but Moss handed back our Kant essays.
我把它夹在你的书里面了
I picked yours up for you and stuck it in there.
好的  谢谢
Oh, cool. Thank you, man.
加拉格
Gallagher...
你被保释了
You made bail.
是你把我保释出来的
You bailed me out?
-卡尔打电话给我了  -我弟弟卡尔吗
- Carl called me. - My brother Carl?
他说他只认识我这一个有钱人
Said he didn't know any other rich people.
确实
He probably doesn't.
谢谢
Thank you.
你还好吗
You all right?
不算好
Been better.
你会出席庭审的  对吗
You're gonna show up to the trial, though, right?
-会的  -那就好
- Yes. - Good...
我还挺喜欢我那公寓的
I kind of like my condo.
我可不想把它卖掉
I'm hoping to keep it for a while.
放心
No worries.
上车吧  我载你回家
Get in. I'll give you a ride home.
我会把那笔赎金还给你的
And I'll pay you back whatever they charge you for the bond.
告诉我多少钱就行
Just let me know how much.
把支票寄给我就行
Yeah, just mail me the check, okay?
我以后真的不想再见到你了
I don't really want to see you again.
我得随身带着我的箱子
I'm just gonna keep my bag with me.
我要去梅诺米尼人保护区
I'm going to the menominee reservation, please.
你知道黄金战斧大赌场在哪吗
You know the Golden Tomahawk Casino?
早上好
Hey. Good morning.
你的电话一直响个不停
Your--your phone has been just going nuts.
一个叫希拉的女人打电话给你
You got a call from some lady named Sheila.
说话糊里糊涂的
Uh, she sounded a bit loopy...
她想雇你在她不在的这段时间里
But she wants to pay you
帮她的植物浇水
to water her plants while she's gone.
好的  她人很好的
Okay, yeah. She's very nice.
利普打了六个电话给你
Uh, and Lip called six times.
我没接  他发了个短信过来
I did--I didn't answer, but he then sent a text,
‘利亚姆今天出院  拜托你到医院来’
Said, "Liam's getting out of the hospital. Please come."
他没事吧
Is he gonna be okay?
-镇定剂打多了  -利亚姆还没出来吗
- Too many downers. - Still no Liam?
-还没呢  -你昨晚上到哪儿去了
- Not yet, honey. - Where were you last night?
-马特家  -谁是马特
- Matt's. - Who's Matt?
你就是马特  那个传说中的马特吗
Oh, you're Matt? "The" Matt?
你他妈都多大了
How fucking old are you?
这是谁
Who's this?
我们的新姐姐和侄子
Our new big sister and nephew.
你好  黛比
Debbie, hi.
加拉格先生
Mr. Gallagher?
利亚姆
Liam!
-嘿  -快让我看看
- Hey, hey, hey! - Look at you!
-小家伙  -你好呀  利亚姆
- Hey, buddy! - Hi, Liam!
我的天哪  我想死你了
Oh, my gosh, I missed you so much!
天哪
Oh, my gosh.
利亚姆是黑人
Liam is black?
-他没事啦  -太好了
- He's all right. - Good!
-宝贝  -快瞧瞧他
- Hi, baby. - There he goes.
-你在干什么呀  -瞧瞧咱们的宝贝
- What are you doing? - Look at you.
-你长大了这么多呀  -小家伙
- You're such a big boy now. - Good boy.
-那是他们的父亲吗  -只怕是了
- That's the father? - I'm afraid so.
我们得尽快去拜访一下这家人了
This family's home visit needs to get scheduled soon...
越快越好
very soon.
有人在家吗
Anybody home?
卡尔
Carl?
黛比
Debbie?
有人在吗
Anybody?